[DOOR OPENS]
[KEYS JINGLING]
- [SCREAMS IN FEAR] Ah!
- [SILLY SFX]
Sweetie!
Isn't it beautiful?
I had it made so we can sell
our vinegar better
because of your beautiful face!
- How much did you spend?
- Nah, it's free
because your Uncle Dennis
used that as his payment to me.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
I picked it up myself
since I was going here anyway.
How much do you need?
Oh, wow.
Do you think borrowing money
is all I know?
Well, since we're already
on that topic,
can I borrow 500 pesos
to get my teeth checked?
500 pesos?!
But, we were supposed to use it
to pay rent
plus we still have some debts...
You should share your blessings!
[JUNE CLICKS TONGUE]
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[JUNE MUTTERING
UNDER HER BREATH]
[PHONE BEEPS]
- Score!
- Hmm.
- Thanks!
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'll get going now.
- You should've gone earlier.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Oh, and...
the electric bill...
just arrived.
[SILLY SFX]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
[IMA] Dear, I know
you're exhausted
from job hunting.
But don't worry,
it'll all work out soon.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Is 500 pesos not enough
for you?!
He's crazy! Why'd he come back?
He's absolutely shameless!
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[WHISPERS] Huh? Who is it?
[DOOR OPENS]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS]
Hello! My name
is Attorney Zia Sun,
the family lawyer
of Don Nato Rose.
Oh, isn't he the one on the news
whose yacht caught fire?
Did anyone survive
from the incident?
Actually, an heir survived.
Did you know...
that your father is the cousin
of the cousin of the uncle
of the nephew of the cousin's
cousin of Don Nato?
[SILLY SFX]
What?!
Can you please...
- run it back from the top?
- Ah!
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Why did she close--
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello! My name
is Attorney Zia Sun,
the family lawyer
of Don Nato Rose.
Did you know that your father
is the cousin of the cousin
of the uncle of the nephew
of the cousin's cousin
of the cousin of Don Nato?
[CRICKETS SFX]
In other words, you,
June Sampaga,
are the heir of the Rose
family empire.
Huh... We're finally rich, Ima!
[SCREAMS] No more lonely nights
- with no electricity!
- That's right!
- Good bye, rent!
- Yes!
- We can finally buy a house!
[BOTH CHEERING]
Yes!
On the condition that you'll
marry Don Nato's godson.
What?!
[ZIA GIGGLING]
[QUIRKY JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]